<resources>
    <string name="app_name">KrakowTourGuideApp</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="sukiennice">Cloth Hall</string>
    <string name="sukiennice_desc"> is one of the most recognizable City icons. It is the central feature of the main market square in the Kraków Old Town</string>
    <string name="main_market">Main Market Square</string>
    <string name="main_market_desc">is one of the largest medieval town squares in Europe</string>
    <string name="mariacki">Church of the Virgin Mary</string>
    <string name="mariacki_desc">is a Brick Gothic church adjacent to the Main Market Square in Kraków, Poland. Built in the 14th century</string>
    <string name="wawel_katedra">Wawel Cathedral</string>
    <string name="wawel_katedra_desc">is a Roman Catholic church located on Wawel Hill in Kraków, Poland. More than 900 years old</string>
    <string name="wawel_zamek">Wawel Royal Castle</string>
    <string name="wawel_zamek_desc">is an complex erected over many centuries atop a limestone outcrop on the left bank of the Vistula river in Kraków</string>
    <string name="brama_florianska">St. Florian Gate</string>
    <string name="brama_florianska_desc">Florian Gate is one of the best-known Polish Gothic towers, and a focal point of Kraków</string>
    <string name="barbakan">The Barbican</string>
    <string name="barbakan_desc">The Barbican is a fortified outpost once connected to the city walls.</string>
    <string name="image">image</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="description">description</string>
    <string name="airshow">Krakow airshow</string>
    <string name="airshow_desc">The international air picnic in Krakow. It takes place in June in the old airport</string>
    <string name="museum_wawel">Wawel Castle Museum</string>
    <string name="museum_wawel_desc">The Wawel Castle is a castle residency located in central Kraków. Built at the behest of King Casimir III the Great.</string>
    <string name="museum_main_square_underground">Main Square Underground Museum</string>
    <string name="museum_main_square_underground_desc">The underground museum beneath the Main Square is an archaeological-architectural preserve. This unique complex occupies 3,300 m2, and exhibits traces of settlements from nomadic times and relics of medieval construction </string>
    <string name="museum_colegium_maius">The Collegium Maius</string>
    <string name="museum_colegium_maius_desc">The Collegium Maius located in Kraków Old Town, Poland, is the Jagiellonian University oldest building, dating back to the 14th century</string>
    <string name="museum_pharmacy">Pharmacy Museum</string>
    <string name="museum_pharmacy_desc">Founded in 1946 and part of the Jagiellonian University, the Pharmacy Museum is one of the few museums of that type in the world. Exhibits collected here show the history of pharmacy from the Middle Ages to modern times.</string>
    <string name="museum_cathedral_wawel">Wawel Cathedral Museum</string>
    <string name="museum_cathedral_wawel_desc">The Cathedral has ammassed some unique treasures over the centuries, and here you can have a peak at some of the most intriguing.</string>
    <string name="museum_czartoryski">Czartoryski Museum</string>
    <string name="museum_czartoryski_desc">A rare jewel of a museum with an extraordinary history to match. Famous of course for its Leonardo da Vinci</string>
    <string name="event_museum_night">Night of Museums</string>
    <string name="event_museum_night_desc">Museum Night is extremely popular venture both amongst inhabitants and tourists</string>
    <string name="event_street_theatre">Street Art International Street Theatre Festival</string>
    <string name="event_street_theatre_desc">Over four summer days, you might suddenly find yourself in the middle of a theatre scene. </string>
    <string name="event_film_festival">Cracow Film Festival</string>
    <string name="event_film_festival_desc">The Cracow Film Festival is one of Europe oldest events dedicated to documentary, animation and other short film forms.</string>
    <string name="event_jazz_festiwal">Summer Jazz Festival at Piwnica Pod Baranami</string>
    <string name="event_jazz_festiwal_desc">Each year the Festival expanded presentions beside 31 everyday concert at the Piwnica club for more additional events at the Krakow</string>
    <string name="food_starka">Starka</string>
    <string name="food_starka_desc">is an essential stop for those interested in experiencing high class Polish cuisine. Jozefa 14, Krakow</string>
    <string name="food_stylowa">Stylowa</string>
    <string name="food_stylowa_desc">Located east of the Old Town, in the district of Nowa Huta, Stylowa is one of the most authentic restaurants in Krakow. Centrum C 3, Krakow</string>
    <string name="food_pod_aniolami">Pod Aniołami</string>
    <string name="food_pod_aniloami_desc">The menu offers lovingly prepared, mouth-watering delicacies of Polish cuisine such as homemade lard, Polish and Russian dumplings. Grodzka 35, Krakow</string>
    <string name="food_cyrano">Cyrano de Bergerac</string>
    <string name="food_cyrano_desc">Cyrano de Bergerac ranks among the top restaurants in Krakow and is a treat for visitors looking for a French-style restaurant. Sławkowska 26, Krakow</string>
    <string name="top_places">Top Places</string>
    <string name="museums">Museums</string>
    <string name="events">Events</string>
    <string name="food">Food</string>

</resources>
